<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Recipes</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ime">Torta</string>
    <string name="vreme">Vreme na podgovtovka</string>
    <string name="recept">Nacin na podgotovka</string>
    <string name="Prebaraj">Пребарај по состојка</string>
    <string name="title_activity_how_to_cook">HowToCook</string>
    <string name="btnSearch">Search</string>
    <string name="hello_world"/>
    <string name="textView"> </string>
    <string-array name="spinnerarray">
        <item >select</item>
        <item >chocolate</item>
        <item >chocolatecream</item>
        <item >peanuts</item>
        <item >coffee</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="select">Select grocery!</string>
    <string name="chocolate">Easy chocolate cake</string>
    <string name="chocolatecream">Paincakes</string>
    <string name="peanuts">Chocolate Cupcakes and Peanut Butter Icing</string>
    <string name="coffee">Chocolate Cupcakes and Peanut Butter Icing</string>
    <string name="btnBackRecipes">Back to Recipes</string>
     <string name="ime0">Easy chocolate cake</string>
    <string name="sostojki0">Ingredients:<br>For the cake: </br><br>225g/8oz plain flour</br><br>350g/12½oz caster sugar</br><br>85g/3oz cocoa powder</br><br>1½ tsp baking powder</br><br>
    					1½ tsp bicarbonate of soda:</br><br>2 free-range eggs</br><br>250ml/9fl oz milk</br><br>125ml/4½fl oz vegetable oil</br><br>
						2 tsp vanilla extract</br><br>250ml/9fl oz boiling water</br><br>For the chocolate icing</br><br>200g/7oz plain chocolate</br><br>200ml/7fl oz double cream</br></string>
	<string name="vreme0">Total time: 1 hour</string>		
	<string name="nacin0">Preparation method:<br>Preheat the oven to 180C/350F/Gas 4. Grease and line two 20cm/8in sandwich tins.For the cake, place all of the cake ingredients, except the boiling water, into a large mixing bowl. Using a wooden spoon, or electric whisk, beat the mixture until smooth and well combined.
	    				Add the boiling water to the mixture, a little at a time, until smooth. (The cake mixture will now be very liquid.)Divide the cake batter between the sandwich tins and bake in the oven for 25-35 minutes, or until the top is firm to the touch and a skewer inserted into the centre of the cake comes out clean.
	    				Remove the cakes from the oven and allow to cool completely, still in their tins, before icing.For the chocolate icing, heat the chocolate and cream in a saucepan over a low heat until the chocolate melts. Remove the pan from the heat and whisk the mixture until smooth, glossy and thickened. Set aside to cool for 1-2 hours, or until thick enough to spread over the cake.
	    				To assemble the cake, run a round-bladed knife around the inside of the cake tins to loosen the cakes. Carefully remove the cakes from the tins.Spread a little chocolate icing over the top of one of the chocolate cakes, then carefully top with the other cake.
	    				Transfer the cake to a serving plate and ice the cake all over with the chocolate icing, using a palette knife.</br></string>
	<string name="ime1">Molten Lava Cakes</string>
	<string name="sostojki1">Ingredients:<br>6 (1-ounce) squares bittersweet chocolate</br> <br>2 (1-ounce) squares semisweet chocolatek</br><br>10 tablespoons (1 1/4 stick) butter</br><br>1/2 cup all-purpose flour</br><br>1 1/2 cups confectioners sugar</br><br>
    					3 large eggs</br><br>3 egg yolks</br><br>1 teaspoon vanilla extract</br><br>2 tablespoons orange liqueur</br></string>
	<string name="vreme1">Total time: 30 minutes</string>		
	<string name="nacin1">Preparation method:<br>Preheat oven to 425 degrees F.Grease 6 (6-ounce) custard cups. Melt the chocolates and butter in the microwave, or in a double boiler. Add the flour and sugar to chocolate mixture. 
	    				Stir in the eggs and yolks until smooth. Stir in the vanilla and orange liqueur. Divide the batter evenly among the custard cups. Place in the oven and bake for 14 minutes. 
	    				The edges should be firm but the center will be runny. Run a knife around the edges to loosen and invert onto dessert plates.</br></string>
	<string name="ime2">Chocolate Cupcakes and Peanut Butter Icing</string>
	<string name="sostojki2">Ingredients:<br>12 tablespoons (1 1/2 sticks) unsalted butter, at room temperature</br> <br>2/3 cup granulated sugar</br><br>2/3 cup light brown sugar, packed</br><br>2 extra-large eggs, at room temperature</br><br>2 tablespoons brewed coffee</br><br>
    					1 3/4 cups all-purpose flour</br><br>1 cup good cocoa powder</br><br>1 1/2 teaspoons baking soda</br><br>1/2 teaspoon kosher salt</br><br>
						1 cup buttermilk, shaken, at room temperature</br></string>
	<string name="vreme2">Total time: 50 minutes</string>		
	<string name="nacin2">Preparation method:<br>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Line a muffin pan with paper or foil liners. Sift together the flour, baking powder, baking soda, cocoa and salt. Set aside.In a large bowl, cream together the butter and sugar until light and fluffy. Add the eggs one at a time, beating well with each addition, then stir in the vanilla. Add the flour mixture alternately with the milk; beat well. Fill the muffin cups 3/4 full.Bake for 15 to 17 minutes in the preheated oven, or until a toothpick inserted into the cake comes out clean. Frost with your favorite frosting when cool.</br></string>						
</resources>